https://www.fortfun.biz/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy | Fort Fun
JavaScript is Disabled
For the best experience and to ensure full functionality of this site, please enable JavaScript in your browser.
Skip to main content area.
CONTACT US
Opens mobile navigation.
Click to call.
Donations
We Are Open! Read More About Our COVID-19 Safety Precautions Here
Fort Fun
Fort Fun values the trust its customers place in our company. Accordingly, we adhere to the highest ethical standards in gathering, using and safeguarding customer information that is entrusted to our company.
Use and Collection of Customer Information
Fort Fun does not rent, sell, or exchange information about its customers. Access to information about our customers is restricted to third parties that need access to Fort Fun customer information in order to provide us with operational or other support services. These parties must agree to safeguard customer information in strict compliance with Fort Fun policy.
Fort Fun gathers only the customer information that is needed to administer its business, provide superior service and communicate offers on merchandise and services that we believe will be of interest to our customers.
Accuracy and Security of Customer Information
Fort Fun makes all reasonable efforts to ensure that the customer information we maintain is accurate, timely, and secure.
Personally Identifiable Information
Fort Fun World Wide Web site collects personally identifiable information (such as name, address, telephone number, or e-mail addresses) from Web site visitors only when visitors voluntarily provide such information to us. Fort Fun Web site visitors who do not want their personally identifiable information collected online should not submit such information to Fort Fun.
Children
Only with the Parent’s or Guardian’s permission will Fort Fun will collect personally identifiable information (name, address, telephone number, or e-mail address) from children (individuals under the age of 13) online.
Personally Identifiable Information Collected Automatically
The Fort Fun Web site may collect information that is not personally identifiable from Web site visitors including the visitor’s operation system, browser, domain name, and the specific web pages on the our Web site that are accessed or visited. We only collect this information in the aggregate, and only use it to improve Fort Fun’s Web site.
Home
Donations
FAQ
Employment
Blog
Contact Us
Privacy Policy
Facebook
©2020 Fort Fun - All rights reserved.
